<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chai D Kanchan on Chai Kanchan</title>
    <link>https://www.chaidk.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Chai D Kanchan on Chai Kanchan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 15:47:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.chaidk.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Tablet Computing&#39; - Writing Computer Compatible Cuneiform Software</title>
      <link>https://www.chaidk.me/articles/tablet_computing/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 15:47:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chaidk.me/articles/tablet_computing/intro/</guid>
      <description>Were an ancient Mesopotamian to find themselves flung into the far future of 2018 through some grotesque mishap, they might very well appreciate the ubiquity of our smartphones and tablets. When they&amp;rsquo;re not bursting with distraction and spectacle, these small, oblong artefacts displaying all manner of text perhaps evoke the memories of their clay ancestors, both of which became indispensable tools within their societies.
Working with ancient cuneiform texts on an electronic device is not quite as straightforward as on clay hardware: with the latter, you can just grab a lump of clay and a reed and start writing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tupshar</title>
      <link>https://www.chaidk.me/software/tupshar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 19:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chaidk.me/software/tupshar/</guid>
      <description>Tupshar &amp;lsquo;The Scribe&amp;rsquo; (Akkadian language) Tupshar is a document editing app designed to make it easier to compose and edit texts in the cuneiform script on your Mac. Based off open formats for encoding computer cuneiform, Tupshar lets you produce richly annotated documents, with each word encoding its own cuneiform, transliteration, normalisation and translation representations.
   Write cuneiform documents easily on the Mac      Tupshar automatically converts your transliterations into cuneiform script      Export to Microsoft Word or plain text formats    Download Download the latest release</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAAi</title>
      <link>https://www.chaidk.me/software/saai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 12:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chaidk.me/software/saai/</guid>
      <description>View letters from the State Archives of Assyria offline in a tablet-optimised interface, featuring tabbed panes and glossary lookup.      Search for letters by title, catalogue number, chapter or sender metadata. A keyboard toolbar allows for easy entry of characters used in Akkadian transliteration not easily accessible via default input methods.      Integrated glossary with lookup of headwords in context      View detailed catalogue info.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello world!</title>
      <link>https://www.chaidk.me/articles/helloworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 10:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chaidk.me/articles/helloworld/</guid>
      <description>This is a traditional &amp;lsquo;Hello world!&amp;rsquo; post to check out whether everything&amp;rsquo;s working on this site, which is not only my personal page but also a work-in-progress learning project for web dev. This initial release is made with the Hugo static site generator, as a straightforward static site serves my needs (articles and a portfolio) well. I&amp;rsquo;m developing the theme in concert with the site as part of webdev learning, and as such it&amp;rsquo;s a pretty simple patchwork at the moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAAo-SX</title>
      <link>https://www.chaidk.me/software/saaosx/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 10:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chaidk.me/software/saaosx/</guid>
      <description>Quickly view and search the letters in the State Archives of Assyria database, even offline      Tabbed panes for choosing between cuneified, transliterated, synthesized normalisations or translations of texts.      Integrated glossary with lookup of headwords in context      Map the locations of places mentioned in a letter      Basic support for reading RINAP volumes      On macOS 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAAi Lite Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://www.chaidk.me/software/saai/privacy/lite/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chaidk.me/software/saai/privacy/lite/</guid>
      <description>SAAi does not collect, store, or transmit any user data whatsoever. As a content viewer, it offers no facility for the user to enter and record any personally identifiable information.
Apple will hold information on you as part of your transaction with them when downloading this app from the App Store. For more information, see the Apple Privacy Policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAAo-SX Lite Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://www.chaidk.me/software/saaosx/privacy/lite/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chaidk.me/software/saaosx/privacy/lite/</guid>
      <description>SAAo-SX does not collect, store, or transmit any user data whatsoever. As a content viewer, it offers no facility for the user to enter and record any personally identifiable information.
If you&amp;rsquo;ve chosen to download the Mac App Store distribution of this app, then Apple will hold information on you as part of your transaction with them. For more information, see the Apple Privacy Policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tupshar Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://www.chaidk.me/software/tupshar/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.chaidk.me/software/tupshar/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Tupshar does not connect to the internet and cannot transmit any personally identifiable information pertaining to its users.
If you&amp;rsquo;ve chosen to download the Mac App Store distribution of this app, then Apple will hold information on you as part of your transaction with them. For more information, see the Apple Privacy Policy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>